Finding Aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (University of Michigan) Records, 1892-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Program Evaluation Office, 1972-2007
  - Program Evaluation, 1991-2007
    - Reviews, 1991-2007
      - Mathematics Review, 2006 (Box 227)
      - McNair Program, 1998-2009; 3 folders (Box 209)
      - Mechanical Engineering Review, 2006; 2009 (Box 227)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering External Review, 2002 (Box 227)
      - National Name Exchange Program, 2001 (Box 209)
      - Nuclear Engineering and Radiological Sciences Program Review, 2007 (Box 227)
      - Overall Program Review Survey Results, 2006 (Box 227)
      - Program Reviews, 2006-2008; 2 folders (Box 227)
      - Project Approval Form (PAF), 2005 (Box 209)
      - Rackham Campaign Report and Resources, 2004 (Box 227)
      - Rackham Data and Korean Studies Program, 1996-2007 (Box 209)
      - SGUS Program, 2004 (Box 209)
      - Spring/Summer Research Review, 2001 (Box 227)
      - Statistics and Applied Statistics Program Review, 2007 (Box 227)
      - Statistics Program External Review, 2001 (Box 227)
      - Summer Research Opportunity Program/Emerge, 2000 (Box 209)
      - Summer Research Opportunity Program, 2004 (Box 209)
      - Summer Research Opportunity/Summer Institute, 2006 (Box 209)
      - Task Force on Testing and Training Prospective GSIs Report, 2002 (Box 227)
      - WISE Program, 2000 (Box 209)
- Board of Governors, 1935-2006
  The Board of Governors series (.6 linear feet) spans the years 1935-1961 and is arranged alphabetically. The records document the Board of Governors of the Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies, a body created to oversee the use, expenditure, allocation, and disposition of the income derived from the Rackham Trust Fund. The series consists of agendas and minutes from Board of Governors meetings as well as related correspondence. Materials documenting the Board of Governors, spanning the years 1973-1985, are located in boxes 79 and 80 as a part of the Dean's Topical Files series and materials spanning the years 1981-1987 are located in box 107 as a part of the Administration series.
  - Agenda, 1935-1963; 28 folders (Box 110)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1961; 4 folders (Box 110)
  - Meeting tapes (audiocassettes), 1982-1990
    The Rackham Board of Governors meetings file consists of 39 audiotapes of selected Board of Governors meetings from the years 1982 to 1990.
    - May 6, 1982 (Box 173)
    - November 4, 1982 (Box 173)
    - April 21, 1983 (Box 173)
    - November 24, 1983 (Box 173)
    - Special Meeting, February 10, 1984 (Box 173)
    - May 4, 1984 (Box 173)
    - November 2, 1984 (Box 173)
    - May 2, 1985 (Box 173)
    - November 4, 1985 (Box 173)
    - April 4, 1986 (Box 173)
    - November 10, 1986 (Box 173)
    - November 10, 1987 (Box 173)
    - May 14, 1990 (Box 173)
  - Board of Governors Minutes, 1936-2006
    The Board of Governors, Minutes files consists of meeting minutes, 1936-2006. The minutes complement meeting agendas and recordings received in earlier accessions. The Rackham Board of Governors exists to review the investment strategy of the Rackham endowment funds, approve the annual budget proposed by the Rackham Dean, and enforce the terms of the bequest. Included in this subseries are minutes, agendas, action items, and annual reports from 1936-2006. The minutes are subject to restriction under the Executive Officers records restriction policy.
    - April 27, 1936-June 19, 1939 (Box 221)
    - May 18, 1936-December 5, 1949 (Box 221)
    - October 16, 1939-May 23, 1949 (Box 221)
    - December 5, 1949-May 21, 1956 (Box 221)
    - March 31, 1950-May 20, 1964 (Box 221)
    - December 18, 1956-May 25, 1964 (Box 221)
    - December 15, 1964-April 9, 1969 (Box 221)
    - April 1970-June, 1973 (Box 221)
    - April 3, 1974-June 11, 1975 (Box 222)
    - October 24, 1975-October 30, 1978 (Box 222)
    - May 8, 1979-November 21, 1979 (Box 222)
    - May 13, 1980-October 30, 1980 (Box 222)
    - June 30, 1981-November 6, 1981 (Box 222)
    - May 6, 1982 (Box 222)
    - November 4, 1982 (Box 222)
    - May 4, 1984 (Box 222)
    - November 4, 1985 (Box 222)
    - April 4, 1986 (Box 222)
    - November 10, 1986 (Box 222)
    - May 5, 1987 (Box 222)
    - November 10, 1987 (Box 222)
    - May 9, 1988 (Box 222)
    - May 5, 1989 (Box 222)
    - May 14, 1990 (Box 222)
    - May 13, 1991 (Box 222)
    - May 11, 1992 (Box 223)
    - May 3, 1993 (Box 223)
    - May 2, 1994 (Box 223)
    - May 22, 1995 (Box 223)
    - May 6, 1996 (Box 223)
    - June 9, 1997 (Box 223)
    - June 22, 1998 (Box 223)
    - June 21, 1999 (Box 223)
    - June 19, 2000 (Box 223)
    - May 7, 2001 (Box 223)
    - May 8, 2002 (Box 223)
    - May 16, 2003 (Box 223)
    - June 7, 2004 (Box 223)
    - June 9, 2005 (Box 223)
    - June 22, 2006 (Box 224)
- Institutes, Projects and Programs
  The Institutes, Projects and Programs series contains documentation of several projects and research programs that reported directly to the Graduate School, including the Institute for Human Adjustment, the Rackham Arthritis Research Unit, Michigan Scholars in College Teaching Program, and a number of smaller grant funded studies.
  - Institute for Human Adjustment (IHA)
    The Institute for Human Adjustment (IHA) subseries (1 linear ft.) spans the years 1938-1964, and is arranged alphabetically. The records document IHA and its programs aimed towards applying research findings to problems of human behavior and social services. The records include correspondence, grant proposals, and program descriptions. Materials documenting IHA, spanning the years 1966-1985, are located in boxes 85-86 as a part of the University Units series. Program Evaluations for IHA programs are located throughout boxes 95-106 as a part of the Program Evaluation series.
    - Annual Reports, 1948-1952 (Box 110)
    - Bureau of Psychological Services, 1948-1963 (Box 110)
    - Fenton Community Center, 1938-1963; 3 folders (Box 110)
    - Fresh Air Camp, 1942-1964; 3 folders (Box 110)
    - General Correspondence, 1938-1942; 1951-1962; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Gerontology, Division of
      - Fund for Adult Education, 1955-1957 (Box 110)
      - Office of Vocational Rehabilitation, 1957-1963 (Box 110)
      - Studies and Proposals, 1949-1964 (Box 111)
      - Training Project for Psycho-Social Gerontology, 1957-1959 (Box 111)
    - Institute of Industrial Health, 1958-1964 (Box 111)
    - Metropolitan Community Research Project, 1959-1963 (Box 111)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1938-1961 (Box 111)
    - Reports to IHA, Miscellaneous, 1938-1958; 2 folders (Box 111)
    - Research and Service in Utilization of Human Resources, 1956-1958 (Box 111)
    - Social Science Research Project, 1946-1960 (Box 111)
    - Speech Clinic Miscellaneous Documents, 1939-1963; 2 folders (Box 111)
  - Rackham Arthritis Research Unit, 1954-1964
    The Rackham Arthritis Research Unit subseries (.4 linear feet), spanning the years 1954-1964, is arranged alphabetically. The records document one of the first organizations in the United States established to research rheumatic diseases. The series consists of correspondence, and descriptions of specific initiatives. Annual reports of the Rackham Arthritis Research Unit, spanning the years 1946-1971, 1981-1987, are located in the Rackham Arthritis Research Unit (University of Michigan) collection held at the Bentley Historical Library.
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1957-1963; 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Operating Budgets, 1945-1951 (Box 111)
    - United States Public Health Service Grant A 512, 1956-1962 (Box 111)
  - Michigan Scholars in College Teaching Program
    The Michigan Scholars in College Teaching Program was founded in the early 1960s to interest promising undergraduate students in several Michigan universities and colleges in careers as college teachers. Most of the sponsored seminars were held in Ann Arbor. Included are some annual reports and correspondence with other universities and colleges and with cooperating departments within the University of Michigan.
    - Topical File
      - Annual Reports
        - 1961-1963 (Box 17)
        - 1965 (Box 17)
        - 1966 (Box 17)
      - Carmichael, Oliver C., 1962-1964 (Box 17)
      - Conference, 1964-1967; 6 folders (Box 17)
      - Coordinators Meeting, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 18)
      - Departmental Conferences (Box 18)
      - Foreign Language Examinations (Box 18)
      - Michigan Committee (Box 18)
      - Position Paper (Box 18)
      - Seminar, 1965 (Box 18)
      - Spurr, Stephen H. (Box 18)
      - Study of Faculty of Cooperating Colleges, circa 1962 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence with Cooperating Colleges, circa 1961-1967
      - Albion College (Box 18)
      - Alma College (Box 18)
      - Calvin College (Box 18)
      - Hope College (Box 18)
      - Kalamazoo College (Box 18)
      - University of Detroit (Box 18)
      - University of Michigan (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Departmental Cooperation
      - Anthropology (Box 18)
      - Art (Box 18)
      - Astronomy (Box 18)
      - Botany (Box 18)
      - Business Administration (Box 18)
      - Chemistry (Box 18)
      - Classical Studies (Box 18)
      - Economics (Box 19)
      - Education (Box 19)
      - Engineering (Box 19)
      - English Language and Literature (Box 19)
      - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 19)
      - Geography (Box 19)
      - Geology (Box 19)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 19)
      - History (Box 19)
      - History of Art (Box 19)
      - Journalism (Box 19)
      - Library Science (Box 19)
      - Linguistics (Box 19)
      - Mathematics (Box 19)
      - Music (Box 19)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 19)
      - Pharmacy (Box 19)
      - Philosophy (Box 19)
      - Physical Education for men (Box 19)
      - Physical Education for Women (Box 19)
      - Physics (Box 19)
      - Political Science (Box 19)
      - Psychology, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Romance Languages and Literatures (Box 19)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 19)
      - Sociology (Box 19)
      - Speech (Box 19)
      - Zoology (Box 19)
  - Projects and Programs, 1950-1957
    The Projects and Programs subseries (.2 linear feet), spanning the years 1950-1957, is arranged alphabetically. It consists of correspondence and grant proposals specific to a small number of programs and projects reporting to the Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies.
    - American Airlines Faculty Grant, 1956-1957 (Box 111)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Contract and Grant), 1950; 1956-1957 (Box 111)
    - Great Lakes Collateral Data Exploration, 1957 (Box 111)
    - Limnology Study of Northern Lake Huron, 1955-1956 (Box 111)
    - Rackham Sociological Research, 1942-1946 (Box 111)
    - Volta, Alessandro, Memorial Fund, 1952 (Box 111)
- Administrative Files, 1874-2010
  - Administrative Files, 1874-1985
    The Administrative Files, 1874-1985 subseries (2 linear feet) include interoffice and campus-wide mass mailings to students, faculty, departments, and schools from 1912-1987. Data on financial aid for graduate students is documented, as is a history of administrative systems and processes within Rackham. Furthermore, a large amount of statistics dating back to the early part of the twentieth century documents graduate degree information.
    - Academic Services Board
      - Meeting Materials, 1976-1988; 2 folders (Box 133)
      - Student Psychiatric Emergency Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 133)
    - Administrative Council Meeting Materials
      - 1975-1983, 2 folders (Box 133)
      - Summary Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 133)
    - Budget Materials, 1977-1983 (Box 133)
    - Deans Meetings, 1977-1980; 1982; 1985-1986 (Box 133)
    - Definition of Terms Committee (Report of), 1977 (Box 133)
    - Executive Board
      - General, 1977-1986 (Box 133)
      - Committee Appointments, 1976-1988 (Box 133)
      - Meeting Materials
        - 1974-1982, 2 folders (Box 133)
        - 1974-1987, 2 folders (Box 134)
      - Members, 1977-1987 (Box 134)
    - Forms and Letters Notebook, circa 1970 (Box 134)
    - Information System History, 1974 (Box 134)
    - Meeting of Department and Program Chairmen, March, 1981 (Box 134)
    - North Central Association, 1979 (Box 134)
    - Personnel Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 134)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1978 (Box 134)
    - Rackham Reorganization, 1975-1976 (Box 134)
    - Registrar Meeting Materials, 1975-1978 (Box 134)
    - Review Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 134)
    - Review and Merger with OVPR, 1983-1985 (Box 134)
    - Statistics
      - General, spans, 1876-1950 (Box 134)
      - Colleges Represented in Graduate School, spans, 1890-1938 (Box 134)
      - Doctoral Degrees Awarded, spans, 1876-1955; 3 folders (Box 134)
      - Graduate Degree Departments of Specialization, spans, 1890-1956 (Box 134)
      - Graduate Degrees Granted
        - General, spans, 1848-1956 (Box 134)
        - Years and Number, spans, 1848-1956 (Box 134)
        - Graduate Degrees (by department and student), ), 1953-1964 (Box 134)
  - 1971-2010
    The Administrative Files, 1971-2010 subseries is divided into seven sub-subseries: Alliances for Graduate Education and the Professoriate (AGEP), Dean's Group Files, Financial, Meetings, Rackham Renovation Records, Searches, and University Press. AGEP, formerly known as the Minority Graduate Education Program, is a program funded by the National Science Foundation to advance minority students pursuing degrees in science, technology, engineering and mathematics (STEM) and Social Behavioral and Economic Sciences (SBE), and prepare them for faculty positions in these areas. These files include budget materials, proposals, reports, and correspondence concerning the program. The Dean's Group Files documents the activities of the dean's group, which includes the associate and assistant deans and meets at least once a month to review financial and other administrative matters, and contains agendas, reports, and other meeting materials. The Financial sub-subseries contain budget and funding files, including several relating to block grants, which can be used by Rackham programs for fellowships, summer support, recruitment activities, research support, and research related travel. The Meetings subseries includes minutes, agendas, and reports from the Executive Board, Rackham Leadership Team, and other groups. The Rackham Renovation Records files consists of records relating to the renovation of the building in the early 2000s, including architectural drawings, budget material, and correspondence. Searches contains files on searches for deans, associate deans, and assistant deans. The subseries of the University Press, which used to be a subordinate unit of Rackham, includes records relating to its finances, facilities, and personnel.
    - Alliances for Graduate Education and the Professoriate (AGEP)
      - 1998-2002
        - Activities and Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 209)
        - All Budget Information, 1999-2000 (Box 209)
        - Annual Report and Budget, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Baseline Data, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Budget Submission, 2000 (Box 209)
        - Budget, 1998-2000 (Box 209)
        - Cost Sharing Report, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Costsharing Policy, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Earl Lewis Resume, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Faculty Leadership Committee, 2000 (Box 209)
        - Interim Progress Report, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Math Workshop, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Minority Programs, 1998 (Box 209)
        - Miscellaneous Forms and Information, 2000 (Box 209)
        - Presentation, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Proposal Backup Forms and Reports, 1998 (Box 209)
        - Proposals and Hiring Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 209)
        - Proposals, 1998 (Box 209)
        - Publicity and SROP Information, 1998-2000 (Box 209)
        - Report Submitted by Robin Rennie, 2002 (Box 209)
        - Report, 1999 (Box 209)
        - Submitted Budget, 1998-2001 (Box 209)
      - 2000-2010
        - Accomplishments and Progress (Box 205)
        - Advocate Program, 2006 (Box 205)
        - AGEP -- LSAMP Position Posting, 2005 (Box 205)
        - AGEP Budget, 2007 (Box 205)
        - AGEP Magazine, 2006 (Box 205)
        - Alliance Meeting Steering Committee, 2006 (Box 205)
        - Annual Retreat and Reports, 2010 (Box 205)
        - Annual Retreat, 2009 (Box 205)
        - Award Notice, 2004 (Box 205)
        - Budget Correspondence, 2008 (Box 205)
        - Budget Matters, 2007-2008 (Box 205)
        - Budget Status Report, 2004 (Box 205)
        - Capacity Building Meeting, 2007 (Box 206)
        - CRLT and NCID Program Proposals, 2007 (Box 206)
        - Data, 2006-2007 (Box 206)
        - DRDA Proposals and Grants, 2004 (Box 206)
        - Evaluation Briefing, 2008 (Box 206)
        - Fall Conference and NSF Reverse Site Visit, 2005 (Box 206)
        - Focus Groups, 2006 (Box 206)
        - General Budget, 2005-2008 (Box 206)
        - Graduate Fellowship Peer Mentoring Program, 2006-2007 (Box 206)
        - Graduate Student Staff Assistant Position, 2006-2007 (Box 206)
        - Guidelines, 2003 (Box 206)
        - Howard Adams Mentoring Workshop, 2006 (Box 206)
        - Job Information and Interviews, 2002-2004 (Box 206)
        - Letter of Intent, 2001-2004 (Box 206)
        - Meeting, April 2007 (Box 206)
        - Meetings, 2006 (Box 206)
        - Miscellaneous, 2005-2007 (Box 206)
        - MSU Conference, 2006 (Box 206)
        - New AGEP Graduate Course, 2006 (Box 206)
        - NSF-AGEP Grant, 2004 (Box 206)
        - Orientation for AGEP Students, 2006 (Box 206)
        - Postdoc Programs, 2006 (Box 206)
        - Postdocs, 2007 (Box 206)
        - Program Manager Position, 2008 (Box 206)
        - Proposal Approval Form, 2004 (Box 206)
        - Proposals and Grants, 2003-2004 (Box 206)
        - Puerto Rico University Visit, 2000; 2003-2004; 3 folders (Box 206)
        - Report Submitted by Christopher Pierre, 2002 (Box 206)
        - Retreats, Meetings, and Budgets, 1998-2007 (Box 206)
        - Sputnik Meeting, 2007 (Box 206)
        - Steering Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 206)
        - Steering Committee Meeting, 2010 (Box 206)
        - STIET IGERT Program, 2006 (Box 206)
        - Teaching Postdoc, 2007 (Box 206)
    - Dean's Group Files
      - September 1998-April, 1999 (Box 210)
      - May 1999-March, 2000 (Box 210)
      - May 2000-October, 2001 (Box 210)
      - December-July, 2005 (Box 210)
    - Financial
      - Application and Grant forms, 2006-2007 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant Allocations, 1999 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant and Graduate Degree Information, 2005-2006 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant Letters, 2002 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant Presentation, 1999 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant Presentation, 1999-2001 (Box 206)
      - Block Grant, 2000 (Box 206)
      - Budget and Fellowship Information, 2006-2008; 3 folders (Box 206)
      - Budget Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 207)
      - Budget Meeting, 2007-2008; 3 folders (Box 207)
      - Budget Requests, 2000 (Box 207)
      - Budget, 2001; 2003-2004; 3 folders (Box 207)
      - Discretionary Funds, 2006 (Box 207)
      - Financial Operations, 2007 (Box 207)
      - Grants and Awards, 2006-2007 (Box 207)
      - GSRA Stipends Information, 2005 (Box 207)
      - Lipschutz/Host/Smith Awards, 2005-2006 (Box 207)
      - Mastercard Purchasing Program Guide Book, 1998 (Box 207)
      - Predoctoral Fellowship Information, 2006-2007 (Box 207)
      - Project Award Change, 2006 (Box 207)
      - Rackham Budget Book, 2000-2001 (Box 207)
      - Rackham Financial Aid Presentation 6+1 Group, 2003 (Box 207)
      - Rackham Graduate Student Research Grant, 2006-2007 (Box 207)
      - Rackham Merit Fellowship Information, 2008 (Box 207)
      - Rackham Merit Scholars Reception, 2006 (Box 207)
      - Requests-Discretionary Funds, 2000 (Box 207)
      - Sociology Funding, 2006 (Box 207)
      - Sokol International Fellowship, 2002 (Box 207)
    - Meetings
      - CoE Graduate Chairs Meeting, 2004-2006 (Box 207)
      - Dean's Group Meeting Minutes, 2005; 2 folders (Box 207)
      - Dean's Group Meeting Minutes, 2006-2011; 4 folders (Box 208)
      - Electronic Dissertation Meeting, 2001; 2 folders (Box 208)
      - EMERGE Committee Meeting, 2000; 3 folders (Box 208)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 2006 (Box 208)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 2007 (Box 208)
      - Executive Board Meeting, 2009-2010 (Box 208)
      - Executive (Box 208)
      - Board Meeting, 2011 (Box 208)
      - IR Core Meeting Notes, 12/1/1999 (Box 208)
      - IR Core Meeting Notes, 1/12/2000 (Box 208)
      - IR Core Meeting, 2001-2003 (Box 208)
      - LS&A Graduate Chairs Meeting, 2005 (Box 208)
      - Meeting with Malayappan Shridhar, 2008 (Box 208)
      - MMPEI Meeting, 2008 (Box 208)
      - Natural Science Graduate Chairs Meeting, 2006 (Box 208)
      - NCID Advance Meeting, 2006-2007 (Box 208)
      - Rackham Leadership Team, 2008-2009 (Box 208)
      - Society of Engineering Science Meeting, 2003 (Box 208)
    - Rackham Renovation Records
      - Design Development, 2001 (Box 228)
      - Furniture, 2 folders (Box 228)
      - Knoll Communication, 2001 (Box 228)
      - MOVE Activation, 2003 (Box 228)
      - MOVE Back, 2002 (Box 228)
      - MOVE, 1997 (Box 228)
      - Programming, 1999 (Box 228)
      - Relocation, 2001 (Box 228)
      - Renovation, General, 2001 (Box 228)
      - Renovation Communication, 2003 (Box 228)
      - Renovation Construction Phase II, 2002 (Box 228)
      - Room 1014, 1997 (Box 228)
      - Schematic Design, 1999 (Box 228)
    - Searches
      - Assistant Dean, 1985 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean Faculty Programs, 1991 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean for Students, 1975 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean Minority Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean Minority Affairs, 1984 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean Minority Affairs, 1984-1989 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean, 1977 (Box 195)
      - Associate Dean, 1988 (Box 195)
      - Graduate Dean Reappointment, 1978 (Box 195)
      - Graduate Dean, 1971 (Box 195)
      - Graduate Dean, 1974 (Box 195)
      - Graduate Dean, 1984-1985 (Box 195)
    - University Press
      - Acumen Publishing, 2000 (Box 229)
      - Colin Day Reappointment, 1992-1994 (Box 229)
      - Director Search, 1987-1988; 2001; 2 folders (Box 229)
      - Director, 1987-1994; 2001; 2 folders (Box 229)
      - English Language Institute, 2000 (Box 229)
      - Executive Committee, 1997 (Box 229)
      - Facilities, 2000-2002 (Box 229)
      - Financials, 2001 (Box 229)
      - General, 1986-1994; 3 folders (Box 229)
      - Overview of the Press, 2001 (Box 229)
      - Personnel, 2000 (Box 229)
      - Reports, 2001 (Box 229)
      - Review of the Press, 2000; 2 folders (Box 229)
      - Warehouse, 2001 (Box 229)
- Degree Lists
  The degree lists series lists the names of students awarded graduate degrees, from the first graduate degrees granted in 1849 and extending through August 1994. The series provides a unique glimpse of the Graduate School, its growth through the years; the change in Rackham's demographics over the years; and the changes in the fields represented at Rackham. The series is organized in three subseries: Degree Lists - Chronological, Degree Lists - Field of Study, and Doctoral Degree Lists.
  - Chronological Degree Lists, 1849-1994